Controversy... what controversy?
Fahrenheit 9/11 is a documentary film directed by Michael Moore.
Michael Moore's view on how the Bush administration allegedly used the tragic events on
9/11 to push forward its agenda for unjust wars in Afghanistan and Iraq.
Self, played by Michael Moore.
Self, played by John Conyers.
Self, played by Abdul Henderson.
Self, played by Craig Unger.
Self (archive footage), played by George W. Bush.
Self (archive footage), played by Saddam Hussein.
Fahrenheit 11/9 is a 2018 American documentary by filmmaker Michael Moore about the 2016 United States
presidential election and first presidency of Donald Trump up to the time of the film's release.
The film is a follow-up to Moore's Fahrenheit 9/11 (2004), a
documentary about the presidency of George W.
The film had its world premiere on September 6, 2018, at the 2018 Toronto International Film Festival,
and was released in the United States on September 21, 2018, by Briarcliff Entertainment.
Despite grossing $6.7 million worldwide, one of the lowest totals of Moore's career,
Fahrenheit 11/9 received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film received a nomination for Best Documentary
Screenplay from the Writers Guild of America.
Three people depicted in the film (Donald and Melania Trump and Kellyanne Conway) collectively received four
nominations at the 39th Golden Raspberry Awards and won three, including Worst Actor for Donald Trump.
The film explores themes of saudi arabia, usa
president, government, politics, war on terror.